- [boy 1] Four. Four.
- [boys exclaiming]
- [boy 2] I got nothing right.
- [boy 1] Two.
- [boy 3] Yes!
- [boy 1] Five.
KOREAN
CORRECT ANSWERS
- [boy 1] Five. Three.
- [boy 4] I only got one right. All right!
- [boy 5] You're going fast.
- [boy 1] Four.
- [groans] Oh my god!
- [boy 4] Dude, I didn't get four.
- I keep getting everything wrong!
- [boy 1] Two. Three.
- Three.
- [murmured conversation]
- [boy 1] One.
- [boy 5] I can't hear it.
[silence]
[boy 5] Whoa. Who did that?
[tense music playing]
[boy 5] What happened?
[boy 2] What's goin' on?
[boys continue whispered conversations]
- Is he okay?
- He seems pissed.
- Yeah, I see that.
- Yeah, super pissed.
- See that?
- What's going on?
- What?
- Man…
Quiet…
What's his problem?
[creaking]
Stay calm. Dude, just…
[silence]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
CLASS OF 2022 UNIVERSITY ADMISSIONS
SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY: 3
[gentle, uplifting music playing]
YONSEI UNIVERSITY: 7
SOGANG UNIVERSITY: 5
"THE BIRD FIGHTS ITS WAY OUT OF THE EGG"
DEMIAN BY HERMANN HESSE
13 DAYS EARLIER
[scribbling]
[boy] Quadratic formula.
Arrange the unknowns and the constant term
on the left side in descending order,
place zero on the right side,
resulting in ax squared
plus by squared plus c equals zero.
[teacher] Hey, Si-eun.
Nice work there.
ENGLISH - CH. 8
MATH - 2021 MOCK TEST
[Si-eun] Imo Mutiny.
An uprising in 1882, in the 19th year
of King Gojeong's Joseon Dynasty reign.
Soldiers of the old army rebelled
against military reforms,
unpaid wages and discrimination
compared to the modern Pyolgigun unit.
This triggered Heungseon Daewongun
to seize power again.
[scribbling]
[Si-eun] Active voice.
The object of the active voice becomes
the subject of the passive voice
in pattern four.
A pattern four sentence has two objects,
so it can be written
as two passive sentences
with each object as a subject.
MOCK TEST IN 13 DAYS
[gentle, uplifting music continues]
[boy 1] Okay!
All right, that's fine. So, uh…
- No, seriously?
- [boys chatting]
Everyone, two of you received an award
in the Intramural Mathematics Competition.
Yeon Si-eun, Jeon Yeong-bin. Come up here.
- [all] Ooh!
- All right!
[boy 2] Congrats.
[teacher] "Yeon Si-eun, gold prize."
"This student won the above prize at the
2022 Intramural Mathematics Competition
and is hereby awarded this certificate."
Nice work, Si-eun.
"Jeon Yeong-bin, bronze prize."
- I'm handing you the same certificate.
- Give it up!
- [cheering]
- Thank you! High five!
[teacher] We are now less
than two weeks away from the mock test.
Have you all been preparing for it?
[all chorus] Yes.
Take this mock test seriously
so you're prepared
when taking
the real college entrance exam.
- [pop music playing]
- [boy 1] With more passion.
- That's it! [laughs]
- [boy 2] Shake it. Shake it.
- Yeah, like that.
- [clattering]
[boy 2] Twirl more.
[boy 1 laughs]
[boy 2] It's okay,
but shake your ass some more.
- Aah! [laughing]
- Yeah. Good. Ooh, shake it. You're sexy!
- [boy 1] Shake your body.
- Oh shit…
Agh! No. You're supposed
to turn around, dumbass.
[music stops]
[boy 2] Fucked it up again.
Hey, you know that people
freaking love your videos, right?
You'll be a celebrity in no time
if you keep it up.
Listen to me.
Your family's poor as shit,
no connections,
and you don't fucking study.
This is the only way you'll survive.
Aren't you grateful?
- Thanks… a lot.
- [boy 3] …rather see me play video games…
If you're grateful, get me a Gatorade.
- [boy 2] Oh, I want Milkis.
- [boy 1] Gimme a Coke Zero.
- Okay.
- [all laugh]
I don't think he suffered enough.
[boy 1] He needs his ass kicked some more.
[boy 4] Exactly.
You gonna have your notes done?
- Hey.
- [boy 1 laughs]
Give me that.
- [boy 2] What are you gonna do?
- [boy 1] What?
- Ooh.
- [boy 2] Whoa.
[Yeong-bin chuckles] You should've
aimed better, asshole. He got hit.
- Yeah, he's right. Why'd you--
- Ay!
Yo, I'm sorry about that. Go study.
I'm sorry.
Next time, be careful.
- [all] Oh…
- [boy 2] Oh-ho!
He's so in for it now, man.
[laughs]
[tense music playing]
[Yeong-bin] It was a mistake.
I said it was a mistake.
- Are you rubbing my face in it?
- Be careful…
not to make more mistakes.
[sighs] Shit, man.
Hey.
You know what?
Everyone thinks you're full of yourself.
No matter what you say,
you make it sound irritating.
Don't you think?
You must be bored.
What?
You should go expand your vocabulary.
[writing]
Wanna die?
[drops pen]
BYUKSAN HIGH SCHOOL
[scoffs]
[player 1] Which one of you is Ahn Su-ho?
Su-ho-ya. Ahn Su-ho.
- Hmm?
- Ahn Su-ho!
[Su-ho] What's up? It's lunchtime already?
[player 1] Was it you?
Did you…
- [sniffles] Did you hit on Na-eun?
- [Su-ho] Na-eun?
Lee Na-eun?
Park Na-eun. Park Na-eun?
Son Na-eun, you fucking shithead!
Oh. She kept DMing me,
but she's not my type.
We went to eat, like, one time,
but I'm not into her.
- Hey, what's for lunch today?
- This…
- J… jaeyuk.
- Sounds good.
Protein is good.
I'm hungry.
Hey!
[upbeat music playing]
Uh, stay back.
[students gasping and exclaiming]
Hey!
[players yelling]
[students gasping]
- [player 2 yelps]
- Yah!
- You got scared.
- [player 3] Hey!
[grunting]
Ah…
Oh shit…
Asshole!
- [wails]
- [bats clatter to floor]
Hey, hey. Hey, come here.
Hey.
You want more?
Asshole!
Whoa!
[player 1] Ow, ow, ow!
- [Su-ho] Hey, hey, hey.
- Ow! Let go of me.
[Su-ho] Should you be doing this,
as athletes?
[player 1] Damn it!
[screams]
[groans] Okay!
Fine! Fuck!
That hurt!
Son of a bitch. Hey, shithead!
[students gasp]
[all] Whoa!
- [all] Whoa!
- [clattering]
[sighs] You went too far.
You fucking shithead!
- [gurgles]
- [thud]
[boy 4] Oh. How is he?
- [Su-ho sighs]
- [boy 5] He's okay.
Hey, take him to the nurse.
I'll kill you if you tell 'em
hyeong did it.
- Hmm?
- [player 1 sighs] Shit.
- [murmuring]
- [boy 5] Well, that was a mess.
- Come on, let's take him to the nurse.
- [boy 4] Yeah, let's go.
Help me help him up.
[boy 6] Wanted them to…
Oh, uh, was that my fault?
- [boy 6] Want to see him take 'em all on.
- Yeah.
[Su-ho] Oh.
[pens and pencils clattering]
Sorry, man. It's my bad, okay?
Hmm.
Fight outside.
[boy 4] Yeah, a proper fight.
Think it might be cool.
NATIONAL EXCELLENCE AWARD IN MATHEMATICS
[man] Massages are great,
but that's not all the team needs.
You need to eat better to gain strength.
- Exactly.
- [door keypad bleeping]
If I catch you trying to sneak out
like last time, it'll be the end of you.
- [door slams]
- Okay?
- All right. Yeah, I'll see you later.
- [lock bleeps]
Hey, kiddo. You're home.
I'm heading out
for another off-season training camp.
I'll be gone a couple of weeks.
Call me if you need to.
Okay.
Your teacher called today.
She said you won first place.
"Yeon Si-eun, gold prize."
[chuckles]
Si-eun-a, you know that this…
this is the reason I exist, right?
I'm really proud of you.
Okay.
[phone buzzing]
[father] Yeah? What?
I already did that. I let them all know.
[woman on video] That should make it
easier to understand.
We can move on now, right?
The number of intersection points
can be determined
by drawing each graph
and identifying where they cross.
[knock at door]
[woman] As you can see
by this example…
[stops video]
[father] You two stay in touch?
I'm just studying right now.
I'm heading out.
- [Si-eun] Have a good time.
- [father] Bye.
[lock bleeps]
[door slams]
Is all that clear?
[sighs] I want you all to know
that my son is number one at his school.
Okay? But I never force him to study.
Why? He's self-motivated.
As I always like to say,
when it comes to your studies…
BYUKSAN HIGH SCHOOL
[birdsong]
[snoring]
[lights buzzing]
[Su-ho] Damn it. [sighs]
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[laughter]
- Oh! Ooh. Holy shit, she's hot.
- [bully 1] Let me see.
- [Yeong-bin] Turn your phone round.
- Whoa!
- [Yeong-bin] Show me your phone.
- [bully 2] Look at her.
- So my type.
- [bully 1] Why set her up with him?
- [bully 2] Why the hell do you think?
- [bully 1] Look in a mirror, bruh.
- Look at your baby muscles, bro.
- [bully 1] You mean these guns?
[bully 2] Nah, your rizz is shit.
- [bully 1] Should I just give up and die?
- [Yeong-bin] Hey, I'll set you up too.
[bully 1] Stop messing with me, man.
[bully 1] I'll give her to you…
if you beat me in arm wrestling.
- Think you can handle it?
- [bully 1] Ask him.
[bully 2] Who do you think will win?
- [bully 1] Answer him.
- [Yeong-bin] Why are you staring?
What? You need something?
- Yo, I could snap you like a twig.
- [hisses]
[bully 2 tuts]
- [chair scrapes]
- [bully 1] Let's go.
- Look at how big my muscles are.
- That's not a muscle.
- You think it's a ball sack or somethin'?
- [bully 2] Yo, bro!
[chuckling] Why would you
call it a ball sack? You weirdo.
[tense music continues]
- [boys panting and groaning]
- [boy 1] Oh God, my legs.
[panting]
[boy 2] Let's go! Hey. Keep it up.
Keep it up! Keep it up! Hey!
Hey! Let's go!
[upbeat music playing]
Yeah!
Whoo!
- [bleep]
- Six minutes 12 seconds.
Hey, can you…
can you take off five seconds?
[coach] Su-ho-ya,
consider applying to sports colleges.
You'd make the cut.
I'm not planning to compete
in the Olympics.
I'll think about it once I beat
my bro Bolt's record, okay?
Your bro Bolt? Who's that?
[panting] You don't know Bolt?
Usain Bolt.
- Nice work.
- This kid. [chuckles]
[bleep]
- 6.45.
- How many?
[boy 3] Come on. Come on. Come on.
[boy 4] Yes, I'm tired.
[boy 3] You can get water at the fence.
- [sighs]
- [boy 5] Yeah.
- That's the best one.
- [boy 4] You're not? Oh my God, my legs.
Aah.
- [boy 6] Whatever. Go.
- [boy 4] Keep going.
- [groaning]
- [boy 4] You're killing me.
- [boy 3] After? At lunch?
- [boy 4] No. My mom made…
[coach] You're almost done.
Stay strong and keep running!
[Yeong-bin] Look how he runs.
[bully 1 chuckling]
[bully 2] Fuck, man. He's like a zombie.
- [moaning]
- [bully 1 laughing]
[bully 2] He'd be faster
running like this.
- [all laughing]
- [bully 1] Hey, I doubt that.
[bully 2 snarling] I'm the world's fuckin'
fastest speed-walking zombie!
[laughter]
[bully 1] Shit.
Get that.
[bully 1] Keep cool.
Don't let him get to you.
What's your name again?
I'm Lee Jeong-chan.
Uh-huh.
[bully 1 sighs]
Ahem. I'm glad you kept your cool.
[panting]
[stopwatch bleeps]
Nine minutes and 48.
- [sighs]
- [coach] Yeon Si-eun.
- Put more effort into getting fit, okay?
- [coughing]
[coach] The healthier you are,
the more you can study.
[panting]
[coach] One of you
take him to the nurse's office.
No need. I'm totally fine.
I'm okay.
[bully 2] "I'm okay."
"Uh… uh, uh… I'm okay."
He was so full of bullshit, man.
He was coughing up a lung.
Yeong-bin-a.
- We need a day when we can beat his ass.
- [bully 2] Yeah. You remember his eyes?
- "Next time, be careful."
- [bully 1] Agreed.
"Be careful not to make more mistakes."
I wanna gouge his fucking eyes out.
- [laughing]
- Hey. Gimme some of that.
[suspenseful music playing]
[bully 2] Ugh, what the hell's that smell?
[bully 1] Ugh, he smells like shit.
Oh. I'm gonna puke.
[giggles]
Stop it.
Do me a favor.
What?
You better leave me alone.
[bully 1 laughs]
[tense music playing]
What are you mumbling about now?
I was clear.
[choking]
[bully 1] Oh, see?
He's just actin' tough. But he's nothing.
[chokes] Let go.
[bully 2] Next time,
be polite when you ask for favors.
Try it again. Properly.
Let go of me.
- Don't.
- Should I say anything?
- Someone should say something.
- Hey, Yeong-bin.
Keep holding.
Let go and I'll kill you.
[man] Hey!
- What's goin' on?
- [coughing]
Ah, yeah, it's not what it looks like.
We were just messing around.
You okay, Si-eun?
- Han Tae-hun.
- [bully 1] Yes?
Well?
- Hey. Don't make us get demerits.
- [Tae-hun] We were joking around.
Think of college.
[sighs]
[man] Yeon Si-eun, you tell me.
Were you joking around?
Yes. We were messing around.
[man] Don't let me
catch you boys again, okay?
[Tae-hun] Yes, sir.
[gentle ambient music playing]
[boy 1] Wait up. Wait up!
It's not like
we're gonna be late. Come on.
[boy 2] Nice.
[boy 1 sighs] No!
[bleeps]
[woman on video] What are
these merchants called? Gongin.
Gongin is also an important concept.
- If Uniform Land Tax Law is in the text…
- [doorbell chimes]
…you can look for the word gongin in
choices one, two, three, four, and five.
- This also works in reverse.
- [chiming]
When you see the word gongin,
look for the Uniform Land Tax Law.
After this, we'll see the implementation
of sangpyeong tong--
- [pauses video]
- [banging at door]
- [banging]
- Who's there?
[Su-ho] Delivery.
I didn't order anything.
[Su-ho] What? No, I got the right place.
[lock bleeps]
What? It's the nerd.
Why are you here?
I didn't order that.
Huh?
Dongbaek Apartment, block 102, unit 902?
It's 101.
[Su-ho] It says 102.
[quirky music plays]
Dang it. Guess you're right
Ahem.
Hey, bro. Cup of water?
- Why should I?
- We're in the same class.
- We're friends. You're being kind of rude.
- [Si-eun] Hey--
[Su-ho] Don't be so cheap.
I'm just asking for water. Right?
- Ugh!
- [lock bleeps]
[Su-ho groans and sighs]
If I get dehydrated and faint,
you wanna be responsible for that?
[sighs] Don't be so mean.
I just asked for water.
But you're just standing there.
I guess I'm gonna faint and die now.
[groans] I'm even losing my voice.
Aah.
[groans]
- Aah!
- Who's the one being rude?
[Su-ho groans]
[sighs] Thanks, man.
I'll buy you three waters tomorrow.
Keep studying hard, hmm? See you later.
And listen to your mom.
Am I doing this right?
[lock whirs]
[lock bleeps]
[teacher] We have a new student.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes. Hello.
Ahem. I'm Oh Beom-seok, yeah.
[Tae-hun] Yeah!
Whoo!
Okay.
Everyone, be nice to Beom-seok.
[musical chiming]
[Tae-hun laughing]
- [Yeong-bin] Check him out.
- [Tae-hun] Should we?
- [bully] Let's go.
- [Tae-hun] Ah! Ahem.
- [bully] Hi.
- [Tae-hun] Ahem.
[Yeong-bin] Oh Beom-seok?
- Yes.
- [Yeong-bin] Where did you transfer from?
- I transferred from Mungang High School.
- [all chuckling] Ooh!
[bully] Dude's got some money.
So you must know Ji-won?
I'm best friends with him.
[Beom-seok] No, I don't know him.
You don't know Ji-won?
You don't know Han Ji-won?
Um, I think I've heard of him,
but I really don't know him at all.
[scoffs]
[tense music playing]
[knuckles cracking]
Move it.
That's my seat.
No thanks.
I said move.
[sighs] I am sick of your shit.
[bully] Not now.
[clicks loudly]
[Su-ho] Why have you all been
so chatty lately?
You won't even let your hyeong sleep.
Can I go back to sleep?
Hmm?
Watch yourself.
[Su-ho groans]
[chair scrapes]
[techno music playing]
- [bully 1] Everybody get one?
- [girl 1] Hurry up!
- [Tae-hun] Let's get drunk!
- [boy 1] Let's go!
[all] Wasted!
- [cheering and laughing]
- [Tae-hun] Yeah!
[boy 1] Yeong-bin,
you're really not drinking?
Again? Why do you keep backing out?
Next week is the mock test,
you fucking idiots.
- [groans]
- [giggles]
[boy 2] Study hard and get
a killer job at a huge corporation.
[laughter]
Yeong-bin-a.
Yeon Si-eun's lost his fuckin' mind
lately, right? He's mouthing off.
What the hell is he gonna do with a pen?
Dumbass.
I mean, even today
when that asshole glared at us,
his eyes looked fucking crazy.
- Almost killed him in front of everyone.
- [bully] Bullshit.
- You were standing still.
- [Tae-hun] Bullshit, you asshole.
I almost snapped his neck.
What do you think
I should do with that guy?
I keep messing with him,
but nothing's working.
That fucking shithead's soul
just won't break. At all.
[boy 3 in background]
Seriously, man? I told you…
Okay. All right, that's fine.
College?
[boy 4 in background] Come on…
Studying is the only thing
he ever cares about.
We'd probably destroy his soul
if we messed with that. It's all he does.
[Tae-hun] What the hell are you saying?
Say it so I can understand.
[bully 1] Your dumb ass
wouldn't understand anyway.
Tell me,
how do you think the narrator feels?
- [papers rustling]
- [teacher 4] Well? Thoughts?
It's anxiousness.
Anxious.
"Even a rustling leaf comes to me."
[electronic music playing]
[cheering]
- [bully] Fine. Real.
- [Tae-hun] Here's another one.
- [bully 1] Which one?
- [Yeong-bin] Not gonna let it slide.
- Hey, hyeong. You're here.
- [Tae-hun] Welcome.
- [girl 1] Hi!
- [girl 2] Hi!
- [all] Whoo!
- [girl 2] He really brought it!
- [girl 1] Awesome!
- That's from Cheonan.
- The trip cost more.
- [bully] I've been waiting for this!
[Yeong-bin] Hey, Hui-ju-ya,
pay your share. You're the last one.
- [bully 2] Good party.
- [Yeong-bin] Pay for his trip.
- [Hui-ju] 100,000?
- [bully 1] This yours?
- [Yeong-bin] Oh, yeah, thanks.
- [Hui-ju] Keep the rest.
- [Yeong-bin] Here.
- [Hui-ju giggles]
[Yeong-bin] Hyeong.
Count it.
I trust you.
[Yeong-bin] Hyeong. Wait up.
- I wanna ask something.
- [bully] We stocked up!
[boy 3] Hey, Yeong-bin.
Where are you going?
[Yeong-bin] My tutor is coming.
- You gonna use those?
- [boy 1] Just go.
- [Yeong-bin] Have fun.
- Thanks, man.
- [boy 1] You're leaving?
- [bully 2] Thank you!
- See ya!
- Where you going?
- [Hui-ju] Let him go.
- [girl 1] Why?
- [boy 2] Be safe.
- [Hui-ju] You don't know?
- Ugh!
- That guy's always leaving.
[Hui-ju] That's how he is.
[echoing clang]
[sounds muffled]
[intense electronic music playing]
[exhaling]
[lighter clicks]
[coughing]
[sounds return to normal]
[techno music playing]
Hyeong.
Your mom came to our place the other day.
She said you haven't been home.
[dealer] Get to the point.
It's not that.
It's about the fentanyl.
What happens if you just stick it on
somewhere on your neck?
You won't feel it as strong.
It's a painkiller, so you'll zone out.
You'll get sluggish and sleepy.
Some people might throw up.
- Why?
- Huh?
Nothing. I was just curious.
- [dealer] Yeong-bin-a.
- [Yeong-bin] Hmm?
Don't screw around too much.
You have nothing to worry about
with me, hyeong.
Bye.
That cheap-ass motherfucker.
[sighs]
[phone bleeps]
[ringing tone]
- [call answered]
- Hey, Ji-won. How have you been?
[gentle pop music playing]
- [phone buzzes]
- [woman on radio] Standard 92.9 FM…
FATHER:
EVERYTHING OKAY?
Your broadcasting station, JPS,
would like to announce that
the time is now 11 p.m. HLQA.
YES
Why don't you reach out to your loved ones
and let them know
that they have done a great job today?
Then we all can--
Wait a minute.
[sighs] We usually only do dead drops.
Next time, we won't meet.
Here.
FENTANYL PATCH
[dealer] Hey. I said a girl.
[man 1] Shit. We almost got screwed.
Move.
- [man 1 laughs]
- What?
You heard. You're in my way.
Well, fuck, man. Maybe you're in my way.
You wanna die?
I don't like the way you're looking at me,
you little asshole.
[clicks]
[man 2] Hey.
Stop staring.
[sighs]
[man 2] You better look away from me
before I break your skull open, fucker.
Hey, hyeong.
[dealer] Go ahead.
Watch who you mess with.
You almost got stabbed.
MOCK TEST IN ONE DAY
[papers rustling]
[door opens]
[Tae-hun] Hey, what's up?
Hey, Beom-seok. The teacher wants you.
- Huh?
- [Yeong-bin] Our teacher wants to see you.
Here.
Thanks, man.
[can opens]
[Yeong-bin] Oh, right.
I heard you had a tough time at Mungang.
[tense music playing]
I talked with Ji-won yesterday.
Huh?
I heard you got your ass kicked
almost every day.
- [grunts]
- [boy] Good one!
[Yeong-bin] Is that why you transferred?
Like a loser?
[chuckles] I mean,
I won't do anything like that to you.
I wanna be your friend.
Sit down.
Okay.
[Yeong-bin] Are you grateful?
I'm going to be your friend,
and I'm gonna keep your secret.
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks, man.
[Yeong-bin] If you're grateful,
do me a favor.
What is it?
[Yeong-bin] Take it.
[papers rustling]
[teacher 2] You know the language section
takes more time, right?
- [students] Yes, ma'am.
- Yes.
[teacher 2] Use your time wisely.
[students] Yes.
[teacher 2] And don't cheat.
[students] Okay.
[Tae-hun] All right!
[clattering]
[tense music playing]
[clock ticking]
[sighs]
There was a bug that landed on your neck.
Boys, what's going on?
Face the front.
[dealer] You won't feel it as strong.
It's a painkiller, so you'll zone out.
You'll get sluggish and sleepy.
Some people might throw up.
[tense music playing]
[Si-eun] In literary expression,
there's a method of representing
the object of expression
by replacing it
with other related ideas or objects.
This includes replacing the substance
with properties of the object
or replacing the whole
with a part of the subject.
These methods can be interchanged
with one another…
[teacher] Hey, where are you going?
[music intensifying]
[panting]
[crashing]
[water running]
[gasping]
[music quietens]
[clock ticking]
[boy 1] What?
[slap]
Oh…
Why are you doing that? What's wrong?
Hey, what is going on with you?
Oh. Nothing.
- [Tae-hun] I can't believe I got none.
- [boy 1] Two.
- [boy 2] Yes!
- [boy 1] Five.
- [boy 3] How many did you get wrong?
- [boy 4] What?
- Three?
- [boy 1] Integrated social studies.
[all exclaiming and laughing]
- [boy 3] I didn't put four on any.
- [boy 4] I'm gonna crush this!
- [boy 1] One.
- [boy 6] What?
- [boy 4] No, it wasn't!
- [boy 1] Five. Four.
- [boy 4] Seriously, that's a mistake.
- [boy 1] Five. Five.
- [boy 5] Shut up.
- [boy 1] Three.
- [boy 6] Yes!
- [boy 1] Two.
- [boy 5] How many did you get?
- [boy 4] Three?
- [boy 1] Five.
- [boy 4] I only got one right.
- [boy 5] Dude, too fast.
[boy 1] Four.
Three.
- One.
- [boy 6] They're the ones that put the--
- [boy 1] Four.
- [boy 6] I can't hear him.
I like when it's all B's.
Just write B every time.
[boy 4] Okay.
[silence]
[Tae-hun] What?
- What's going on?
- What?
Quiet.
[tense music playing]
[Beom-seok] Si-eun, uh,
it's… it's not what you think.
[creaking]
[scribbling]
[Si-eun] Newton's second law.
Force is equal to mass times acceleration.
[scribbling]
[Si-eun] The centrifugal force
of an object
can be used to create a greater impact.
- [Yeong-bin] Ah!
- [all gasping]
[wails]
- Oh my God.
- [Tae-hun yelping]
You fucking lunatic!
[Yeong-bin grunting]
[Yeong-bin groans]
[muffled] Wait! Wait!
[yelping]
[moaning]
[boy] That's like…
I asked a favor.
I said to stop.
- [students exclaiming]
- Oh…
Let's not cross the line, hmm?
Enough is enough.
[boy] That was the line?
You next?
Me? Nah,
you just woke up a guardian angel.
[chuckles]
Funny?
Trying to be.
[all exclaiming]
["Brass Knuckle" by Boi B playing]
♪ Yeah, uh-uh ♪
♪ Word ♪
♪ Brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Um, um… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ You never know… ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Good boy gone bad… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ But I got K2 in my mouth… ♪
♪ Break your fucking neck… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Smells like teen spirit… ♪
♪ Brass knuckle… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ But you don't hear me though ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Good boy gone bad ♪
ALL NAMES, PLACES,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL